[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "But what lessons should we take from tonight's Republican win in this recall election looking ahead to November?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Yes, you know, I think if you are a Democrat, you take a look at these numbers, you say gee, President Obama is still up 11 points in the state by those who voted.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Can you hear that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "-- guards in particular -- I can hear it now, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "When people say why should we care that the Queen is having her 60th anniversary celebration, what do you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Well, the first thing is it emerges very quickly that people do care.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Brooke?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "(Inaudible) on the carriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "The Queen and Prince Charles made that great speech, what did it feel like to be there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Oh, it was fantastic.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "-- the Queen be holding an umbrella in such a carriage?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Oh, they'll have a gilt-edged umbrella, I would imagine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Was he really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "He was actually carriage driving --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"]}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "At the age of 90?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "At the age of 90, 91 on Sunday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Why is she so revered and not just in this country but around the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "I think she represents something that is constant in a changing world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "(Inaudible), aren't you, Brooke?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "I've just never -- I've never, ever seen it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brooke"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "We do, don't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "We do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "How do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Because her husband isn't here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Because it's all about the line of succession.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Out of interest, when you're all standing behind the curtains waiting to come out, what are you all doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Chatting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "About -- about what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Lots of family gossip.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "About what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "And drinking homemade lemon refresher.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Lemon refresher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "I think it's just a great endorsement for the royal family, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "I feel like they've been energized these last four days to a new level again.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "That's not going to happen, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "No, totally false assumption.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Gut reaction to what we just saw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Immense pride to be sitting here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120605pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Very, very emotional.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]